Broc Atkinson

Full Stack Web Developer

720-480-1908 atkinsonbg@gmail.com

SKILLS

Recent graduate from the University of Denver's full stack web development boot camp, using the MERN stack while thoroughly enjoying React. Having a professional background in the hospitality, luxury automotive and legal industry while spending the last 10 years as a paralegal

EXPERIENCE

Bodie Enger Law, Paralegal

August 2017 - PRESENT

- Opposing parties investigation
- Post judgment enforcement
- Legal research and review
- Document drafting
- Settlement negotiation

HindmanSanchez - Paralegal

November 2011 - August 2017

- Tasked with working the largest active caseload of the department
- Foreclosures and Bankruptcy analysis
- Heavy client and general public contact
- Skip trace and evaluate credit reports

EDUCATION

Denver University, — Full stack Web development

May 2019 - December 2019

6 month bootcamp covering the basics into the MERN stack.

Adams State, — Paralegal Certificate

December 2009